shortyawards.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - The Shorty Awards

The Shorty Awards (the "Awards") are owned, operated and distributed by Shorty Awards LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (referred to in this Privacy Policy as "Shorty Awards", "Awards" or "we" and through similar words such as "us," "our," etc.). By PARTICIPATING IN the Awards, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions described below (the "PRIVACY POLICY").

This Privacy Policy outlines the personal data that the Awards may collect, how the Awards use and safeguard that data, and with whom we may share it. This Privacy Policy is intended to provide notice to individuals regarding personal data in an effort to be compliant with the data privacy laws and regulations of the jurisdictions in which the Awards operate. 

The Awards encourage our visitors and other interested parties to read this Privacy Policy. By using our website or submitting personal data to the Awards by any other means, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, and agree that the Awards may collect, process, transfer, use, and disclose your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy. We may, at our sole discretion, modify this Privacy Policy at any time. By accessing participating in the Awards at any time after such modifications, you are agreeing to such modifications. This Privacy Policy was last modified as of May 25, 2018.

During your use of our website or communication with the Awards, personal data may be collected and processed by the Awards. You may affirmatively provide us with certain personal data (such as your name, email address, phone number, mailing address, your likeness through photos or videos, and email receipt and open data, etc.) when participating in the Awards.

  * **Information Collected by "Cookies"** : When you access our website and various other interactive properties from which you can participate in the Awards, we may send one or more "cookies" to your computer. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your browser, which we use to help provide better Awards to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. 
  * **Log File Information** : Our servers automatically record certain information that your browser sends whenever you access our web site. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

Any personal information that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

If you have not opted out from receiving marketing communications from us, we may use your email address, phone number or other personal data to send commercial or marketing messages. We also may use your email address, phone number and other personal data for non-marketing or administrative purposes. You cannot opt out of receiving communications for non-marketing or administrative purposes. Finally, we may run certain algorithms on your personal data as described in our Terms of Service in order to tally votes, rank submissions, ensure fairness in voting process, and provide general security to the Awards.

With regard to non-personal data, we use aggregated information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of our services and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. In addition, we may use “cookies,” clear gifs and log file information to deliver content (which may include third party advertisements) specific to your interests, and remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it each time you visit one of our interactive properties. 

We will not share your personal data with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We may provide personal data to employees, consultants, affiliates or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. In such circumstances, we require that these parties agree to protect the confidentiality of such information and to comply in all respects with this Privacy Policy.

We may share non-personal data (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Awards. 

In addition, we may release personal data: (i) to the extent we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any applicable law, enforce our rules, protect ourselves against any liability, defend ourselves against any claims, protect the rights, property and personal safety of any user or protect the public welfare; or (ii) to respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

In addition, we may release personal data: (i) to the extent we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any applicable law, enforce our rules, protect ourselves against any liability, defend ourselves against any claims, protect the rights, property and personal safety of any user or protect the public welfare; or (ii) to respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

If you are located in the EU, the General Data Protection Regulation grants you certain rights under the law. In particular, the right to access, correct, or delete the personal data the Awards hold about you. The Awards will retain you data for the length of time you engage with us, until you request deletion of such personal data.

Upon request, the Awards will grant individuals reasonable access to personal data that it holds about them. In addition, the Awards will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information it holds about them. The Awards also rely upon each individual to assist in providing accurate updates of his or her personal data. In order to access, correct, amend, or delete the personal data the Awards hold about an individual, the individual should contact [info@shortyawards.com](mailto:info@shortyawards.com).

If you have a comment, question, or complaint about how the Awards are handling your personal data, we hope that you contact us at [info@shortyawards.com](mailto:info@shortyawards.com) in order to allow us to resolve the matter. In addition, individuals located in the EU may submit a complaint regarding the processing of their personal data to the EU data protection authorities (DPAs). The following link may assist you in finding the appropriate DPA: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm>

We may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to them, and we cannot control their activities.

We have implemented security measures to protect personal data collected on the Awards against loss, misuse or alteration. In addition, your account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. It is important that you protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. Moreover, despite the precautions described above, we cannot and do not guarantee that the individual user information you have transmitted will not be intercepted by others and/or decrypted or accidentally disclosed, and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

You must be at least 13 years old to participate in the Awards.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Awards who are participants in the awards to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email with "California Privacy Rights" in the heading to [info@shortyawards.com](mailto:info@shortyawards.com) or write us at: 

**Shorty Awards Privacy Rights**  
588 Broadway #503  
New York, NY 10012 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the services provided by the Awards, please contact us at: [info@shortyawards.com](mailto:info@shortyawards.com)
